Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
My name is Happy Gilmore.
Growing up. I always wanted
to be a hockey player.
But then 30 years ago.
I picked up a golf club.
Turned out to be a
pretty good decision.
And Happy Gilmore wins
the 98th U.S. Open.
I got to marry a great
lady named Virginia.
and we had a son named Gordy.
The wins didn't always
come as expected.
but like Grandma always said.
sometimes it's better
to be lucky than good.
Oh. Lord!
I made it!
Yeah. I was getting lucky
in more ways than one.
He shoots. he scores!
And after our fourth
boy in four years.
Virginia had an idea
for an endorsement.
Trojan. Kids are great...
...in moderation.
What are you doing? Calm down!
I tried to get the boys into
competitive golf tournaments...
Follow that.
But their hockey
instincts were too strong.
Boys. stop! Come on.
what are you doing?
Tiger Woods had a video game.
so we did a Happy Gilmore one.
But I think the computer guys
made it a little too realistic.
You've had enough.
Anyways. the boys loved
how violent it was.
but it made my
little girl nervous.
That's right. we finally
had a little girl.
sweet Vienna. Mommy's
new best friend.
Oh. and I hosted Saturday Night
Live a few times. That was nice.
The Spice Girls are here!
Maroon 5 is here!
The Weeknd is here! So stick
around. we'll be right back.
Yeah. we had it all.
so I told Virginia...
We should just retire so we can
hang out with the kids all day.
We're not done with golf. Happy.
And golf's not done with us.
It's like Chubbs used to
say. We've only just begun.
Hmm.
Gordy!
Oh. come on. don't pee
on the slip-n-slide.
Appreciate your time
today. It's Mother's Day.
We honor all of the
mothers who are watching.
Let's go real deep now!
But in golf. even when you're
at the top of your game...
you can always shank one.
Uh-oh.
After the funeral. I decided I would
never pick up a golf club again.
I was now a single
father of five children.
There was really only
one thing I could do...
I'd never been a big boozer.
but alcohol was the only
thing that helped me
to forget what I'd done to the
sweetest woman I'd ever known.
-Oh. one more thing...
-It's no good.
The money.
Give me the...
No. no. dude! Come on. man.
See. Virginia always
handled the finances.
so without her. a lot of
stuff fell through the cracks.
Should I smash the window?
Then I caught some guy trying
to break into my Ferrari.
Hey. can you hold my beer?
Yeah.
The guy wasn't a thief.
he was a repo man.
Can you let me explain?
Turns out I didn't know
I had to renew the lease.
The big baby sued me.
and I lost everything...
including Grandma's house.
which was devastating.
The boys had to move into
an apartment together.
and me and Vienna found a new
place that was affordable.
It's not the best neighborhood.
but it's walkable to my new job.
Gary. can you pick
up in section 2?
Happy Gilmore. Oh. my God.
I'm such a massive fan.
Okay. bro. what can
I help you with?
You ever hear of
Maxi Sports Drink?
I think that's aisle four.
No. It's my company. I own it.
I'm Frank Manatee.
My real passion is this cutting-edge
golf project that I've been working on.
I don't golf no more. brother.
Cucumber juice in there?
Sure.
Anyway. I figured maybe you
would start golfing again
once you heard how huge
this league was gonna be.
I wish you luck. but
I'm not interested.
See. that's the thing. Nobody's
interested in traditional golf.
It's a boring sport
played by boring people.
They ain't boring.
they're my friends.
You don't understand. You
inspired this thing. all right?
And I love you. and I'd
hate to see you pass this up
and have your life turn out
worse than it already is.
I get it. Golf makes
you tense. right?
Because the whole wife thing?
Get your skunk breath out of
my face. or I swear to God...
Or what. tough guy? You're not
gonna do a damn thing about it.
because if you lay one finger on
me. you're going right to jail.
That's if I get caught.
Operations.
Hey. Linda. can you turn the
security cameras off for 90 seconds?
Seven. eight. Fouetté.
fouetté. Finish.
Great. Arms. fifth. Soutenu.
Fouetté. fouetté.
Arms. fifth.
Soutenu. Chaîné. chaîné.
And arabesque.
Look at that.
Daddy!
Hey. Vienna.
Oh. with the kicks! Hey.
The Rockettes are here.
Glad you're home.
You were a clue on
Jeopardy! Let me show you.
Really?
Okay. Hi.
Hi.
How'd my girl do today?
Great. Beyond great. She needs
a better teacher than me.
-Look.
-Yeah.
With his amazing long drives
and hockey player's temper.
this golfer won the first of his six
Tour Championships in 1996. Carter?
Who is Happy Goldberg?
Sorry. no. Ling.
Who is Happy Gudenstein?
Nope. Jana.
Who is Skippy Goldenbaum?
That is incorrect.
He is Jewish. but we were
looking for Happy Gilmore.
At least he knew it.
I'm making your grandma's
brisket for dinner.
The boys are coming.
Okay. good. Good. I can't wait.
What do you mean. a better
teacher? Are you quitting?
No. but I work at the
Boys and Girls Club.
She's light years beyond
anyone else I ever taught.
So what? Where should she go?
The Paris Opera Ballet School.
Where's that? Around here?
It's in Paris.
They only have four
slots open each year.
I sent them the
videos of Vienna.
and they're saving one
of the slots for her.
Is it free?
How much is it?
$75.000 a year.
I marinated the brisket in ketchup
all day like you said Grandma used to.
Absolutely incredible.
You crushed it. Vivi.
Vienna. you're gonna have
to make more. I'm starving.
Easy. Bobby. Make your own.
-Terry. how about I make you cry?
-Are you freaking kidding?
Yeah! Strangle him! Use it!
Put the fork down! Not the fork.
We fight in the basement.
not at the table.
-Sorry. Daddy.
-Sorry.
It's all right.
How's work going. boys?
I gotta say. Pop. I'm
loving the road crew.
I'm killing it at the car wash.
I'm going for Employee of
the Month at the drugstore.
Whoop. whoop. whoop.
I've been keeping the
sky safe at the airport.
Dude!
You guys wouldn't have to be working
if I didn't lose all our money.
-We don't need no money.
-Money's for snobs.
Everybody needs money
to chase their dreams.
You guys didn't
even go to college
because you thought you had to stick
around here and keep an eye on me.
What are you talking about?
-...we got brisket. we got hockey here.
-...we got food.
I'm just psyched you thought any
of us could get into college.
He's not going to college.
That's what he
was talking about.
It's a turn of
phrase. Not saying...
Turn of phrase? You just said...
Say your phrase.
It makes no sense.
I know what it means.
You turn and you look at
somebody and you say some...
♪ Here. it's never ending Can't
remember when it started ♪
♪ Pass around the lampshade There'll
be plenty enough room in jail ♪
♪ If being wrong's a crime
I'm serving forever ♪
♪ If being strong's your
kind I need help... ♪
I'm telling you now. I'm
getting the waterbed.
What are you talking about?
I shot tied the waterbed.
-Enough out of you.
-What?
You're on the floor.
You popped the waterbed.
-Come on. let's go.
-All right.
-Night. guys. Love you.
-Thanks for coming.
Call me when you get there.
Wait a minute. How
are there four of you?
Wait a minute. Who's steering?
Gordy. don't steer with your feet.
Chips off the old block. huh?
Hey. Uncle John Daly.
Hey. Vienna. Happy.
Hey. pal.
I'm almost out of here. I just
put a down payment on a tent.
Will you stop? I don't
want you to leave.
Stay as long as you need to.
I appreciate you. You want
to come watch Love Island?
I do. but I'm going to
have a couple of nightcaps
and get some rest
for work tomorrow.
Make that scratch. dog.
Absolutely. Good
night. my brother.
Night. night. Love you.
Love you.
Oh. my God. I hope
he marries her.
She going for it.
I should be putting you to bed.
Look. Dad. I know Miss Simon
talked to you about dance school.
but don't even think about it.
When I was a teenager. I
wanted to be on the Bruins.
This is your Bruins.
Except you know how to dance
and I didn't know how to skate.
Did you know Mama
was a great dancer?
Yeah. she was.
Get some sleep. Dad.
Yeah. she was something else.
Good night. Dad.
Good night. Virginia.
I can't believe that
me in cheap lingerie
carrying two pitchers of
Moosehead was your "happy place."
I'm sorry. Virginia.
Oh. sweetie. don't worry. I'm
not here to judge your fantasies.
No. not that. I'm sorry about...
Killing me with a tee shot?
Come on.
You've apologized for
that a thousand times.
Look. Happy. I know you're
worried about the kids' futures.
but you've got to
show them by example.
Let them see the Happy
I fell in love with.
-I'm not that man anymore.
-Mmm.
Okay. No. no. no.
-Please.
-No. no.
Can you just hold on to
that for a second. sweetie?
Honey. you'll always be the
greatest. but you need some purpose.
So I'm gonna tell you
what I always told you.
Okay.
You're not a hockey
player. Happy.
You are a...
Hey. where you going
with those clubs. punk?
Mr. Gilmore. I'm your caddie.
Oh. I'm sorry about that.
No. let me carry these.
They're my grandfather's.
They're old.
You gonna hit that?
I don't know if I can. Johnny.
How are you gonna put Vienna
through ballet school?
You know about that?
Of course. You know
what else I know?
It's $75.000 a year.
That's four years.
That's 333 grand.
That's terrible math.
Johnny. It's 300 grand.
Hey. if you can get a
discount. that's great.
But how you gonna
make that cha-ching?
I don't know.
I thought I'd pick a few double
shifts up at the supermarket. Maybe...
There's only one way you can make some
big dollars fast. Grip it and rip it.
Johnny. I wouldn't even
know where to start.
At the bottom.
Excuse me. I'm looking
to get out there.
There's a threesome going out at
10:15. You can join them. Name?
Don't worry about it.
I won't.
Who was that? Grizzly Adams?
I don't know who that is.
Is it just us three?
No. Starter said a fourth
is playing with us.
-We gotta play with some random?
-Yup.
It's always some yin-yang who
plays like shit and never shuts up.
Oh. man. Is that him?
He looks like he got a
divorce four seconds ago.
Are you the one that's
playing with us?
I think so. yeah.
We like to play quick.
so try to keep up?
Got it.
-Let's get this party started?
-Yeah.
-Yeah. let's get it started.
-Whoo!
Oh!
-Whoo! Cart path!
-Man!
-Nice one. Fitzy.
-Hell yeah.
I will take that all day.
Yes. sir. You got this.
girl. Get that shit.
Ha!
Gotta be happy with that. Sal.
-Top spinner. Just how I drew it up. boys.
-Mmm-hmm.
Check this out.
Xanax arms. head still.
Oh!
-What the hell?
-Holy shit.
Boom! Explosion!
That's my dog!
Mmm-hmm! Took a
lesson at Golf Hut.
-It shows. Stein-man.
-Uh-huh.
Man. I wish I was
included in that.
-Boy.
-He doing the Happy Gilmore swing?
My stupid uncle always
tries that bullshit.
Swings and misses every
time. Pain in my ass.
God. He rolled
further than the ball.
Gonna be a long-ass
day. my dudes.
Hell yeah!
Oh. eat a bag of...
Did you find your ball yet?
Yeah. I found it.
I'm just roaming around in here because
I like poison ivy. you piece of...
Grandma!
Oh. choke on my
dangling. wrinkly...
I don't know why. I get so
intimidated in the sand.
The dude from Golf Hut said
just flip it like a pancake.
-Flip that pancake. Sally.
-Mmm-hmm.
Nice!
♪ To the window. to the walls ♪
♪ To the walls ♪
♪ 'Til sweat drop
down my balls ♪
♪ 'Til all these bitches crawl ♪
♪ 'Til all skeet-skeet.
motherfucker ♪
♪ 'Til all
skeet-skeet. goddamn ♪
♪ A-goddamn ♪
Nice putt. dude. We'll
put you down for a 12.
Yeah.
I think he thinks the
tee-marker's the ball.
Told you.
Hey. DJ Khaled. maybe give the
Happy Gilmore swing a rest?
Because it ain't working.
Yo. that is Happy Gilmore.
Happy Gilmore sucks?
Hey. can you call
fore next time?
Fore!
Whoa.
Hey. man. at least it went in.
It did?
No!
Man. Happy Gilmore is
such a joke. It's sad.
Still got to ask for
his autograph. though.
My auntie used to cream
her jeans for that fool.
Whoa!
Tell your aunt I'll sign
her jeans for $300.000.
I guess I'm a
little rusty. gang.
The Stein-man recently had
a lesson at the Golf Hut.
Yes.
But I just. I haven't swung a
club in ten years. so. sorry.
How about you. Chubbs?
You got any tips for me?
Relax. do what
we talked about.
It's all in the hips.
yeah. it's all in the hips!
It's all...
Oh. yeah. Ease the tension.
Oh. I miss you. baby.
My man having a wet dream
we don't know about?
-Oh. my God!
-Now that is some Happy Gilmore shit!
-Yes. Yeah.
-Unbelievable!
I mean. I've hit some big ones.
but that was a freakin' rocket!
It was. like. effortless.
but still ferocious.
You got to teach me
how to do that. dude.
Dude! Dude!
-Dude!
Remember Happy Gilmore? He's making
news on the golf course again.
And not the good kind.
He was apparently driving a golf
cart while intoxicated last week
and struck another cart.
Stein-man!
Gilmore was arrested and charged with
vandalism and driving under the influence.
Prosecutors agreed to suspend
the golf-cart-related charges
on the condition that Gilmore
refrain from any physical violence
and attend a radical
alcohol treatment program.
Go Bruins!
He was also fired from
his job at Stop & Shop.
Truly. a sad end
for a sports legend.
Thanks for being
with us today.
In 1996. you were arrested for
inciting injury to persons or property.
conspiracy to commit
vehicular manslaughter.
criminal menacing.
and stealing a jacket.
At trial. you were found not
guilty by reason of insanity
and remanded to this facility.
That was 29 years ago.
It feels like yesterday.
Twenty-nine years
is a long time.
and so this board is inclined
to grant you your release.
If we were to do so. what then?
Well. I'd want to give
back to the community.
Especially the children who
are. of course. our future.
And animals. also. who
need to be snuggled.
and neutered with their
permission. of course.
What about Happy Gilmore?
Oh. I would stay far. far away.
Far. far away from Gilmore.
What if you ran into him.
say. on a golf course?
I'd wave or I could
nod. That's also good.
And if he was wearing
a gold jacket?
Incredible!
-Happy Gilmore wins the gold jacket!
-No!
I would fill a pillowcase with golf
balls and beat the piss out of him!
-I would tear the jacket off his back...
-Guards.
...and shove it down his throat!
Bring this animal
back to his cell!
That is my jacket! My jacket!
Shooter's gold! All
mine! It's my gold...
Lunch? Benihana?
-Hell yeah.
Excuse me. Is this where
the alcohol meetings are?
You're in the right place.
How are you feeling?
Mmm. a little shaky.
First five days are rough.
Just get through today and your
body will start turning the corner.
Thank you. And this is all
on the down low. right?
Happy freakin' Gilmore!
I can't believe you be
hitting the bottle too!
I guess Bessie didn't
get the down low memo.
Yeah. that's all right.
Where's the therapist?
He'll be here. He likes
to make an entrance.
Mr. Gilmore?
Holy shit.
As I live and breathe. It
is wonderful to see you.
How's Grandma?
Grandma? Passed away
maybe 15 years ago.
Mmm. That's a shame. I know
you loved on her so much.
Yeah.
Is that when you
began abusing alcohol?
No. no. That actually started
up after my wife got killed.
-Mm. It's always something. isn't it?
-Mmm-hmm.
Okay.
Happy. why don't you
come on up front?
We have a new member here.
Hi. I'm Happy and
I'm an alcoholic.
Oh. we don't say alcoholic.
We're not scientists.
We're just people trying to get
by. We say "alkie". Keeps it light.
Uh... I'm Happy
and I'm an alkie?
Say it loud and proud!
-Hi. I'm Happy and I'm an alkie!
-Ha-ha!
Celebrities. They just like us.
Except they got a lot more cash.
Now. Charlotte. last
week you were concerned
about a musical festival
you were to attend.
How'd that work out?
-Fine. It was a concert.
-Mmm-hmm.
My friends were drinking
and offering me drinks.
but I didn't have any.
But I bet you wanted that
liquor something fierce. huh?
I mean. I was tempted. but...
I bet you would have kicked
your own mother in the face
just to get a sniff of
that liquor. wouldn't you?
Not really.
Charlotte. if we don't stop
lying. we don't stop drinking.
Why won't you stop lying?
Because I'm an alkie?
And how does a degenerate. low-life
alkie take the first step to recovery?
By washing your car?
Bingo! Three o'clock. Thursday?
I got the soap. you bring the rags
and bucket. we make it a party?
-I'm sorry. I have a question.
-Yeah?
What does the car-washing have
to do with the no-drinking?
You're thinking.
Mr. Gilmore's up in his head
when really he should be
listening to me and
keeping his mouth shut.
This is a radical alcohol
treatment program.
And the chief judge.
my Uncle Dave.
he told me that I can do whatever
I want with everyone in this room.
Check out the name tag.
You're in my world now. Grandma.
You're in my world now.
Oh. my gosh.
Welcome to the future of golf.
The greatest game just got
a triple shot of adrenaline.
Experience the
revolution of Maxi.
-Game over. regular golf.
- Wow.
-Pretty great.
-So good.
Yeah. it's something
for sure. What is it?
-I mean. what are we seeing?
-What is it?
So. basically. Maxi is
a reimagining of golf.
It's golf for today.
Why is golf so boring and dumb?
Golf was invented 800 years
ago. something like that.
I thought about
it and I was like.
"If society could change.
how come the rules of golf
have stayed the same?"
And that's why I created Maxi.
-That's deep.
-Yeah.
The NBA. the NFL. the NHL. they
offer the highest quality product.
-Wow.
-And so does Maxi.
You're saying Maxi has the
best golfers in the world?
Oh. my God.
-You doing okay. Frank?
-I think I'm going to die.
That's what's up.
but listen. gang.
how are you going to get
these professional golfers
to play in this new league?
I've already got my golfers
and they're the best.
You think they're
better than the pros?
I don't think. Stat. I know.
You should think about
talking to Happy Gilmore.
I don't know who that is.
-Yeah. tell that to the lobsters.
-Mmm.
Johnny. what are you doing
with those chicken wings?
They've been in the fridge
for three weeks now. bro.
I just put this sauce on them.
It gets rid of all the bacteria.
Hmm. I don't know about
that. but good luck.
When you've done
that. the TV remote.
Always wondered why
that didn't work.
What are you doing
on that contuder?
I'm looking for a job.
There's a new Dairy Queen around
here. I think they're hiring.
You're not going to make
$330.000 at no Dairy Queen.
You know what you got to do.
I tried the golf. The golf
didn't work out. Cuckoo clock.
Grandma's cuckoo clock?
That's sacrilegious. Daddy.
Yeah. I know.
You can't give up
because of one bad round.
You had to at least hit
a couple decent shots.
I think I hit one out of 117.
Yeah. next time you'll hit two
and then three. and before you
know it. you're the best again.
I'm 58 years old. V.
Forget about being the best.
If you finish 30th in
the Tour Championship.
-you make 100 grand. brother.
-How am I going to finish 30th?
I lost to three idiots
on a municipal course.
You were hammered.
Maybe you need to practice.
Dad. like I do with dancing.
What else are you going to do.
sober boy? You can't drink.
Hand sanitizer.
Let Uncle John
take care of that.
This is hand sanitizer.
Gotcha.
-Were you Happy Gilmore?
-Shh.
Um. do you want
to try some clubs?
I do. yes.
Here. try the six iron.
A lot of pros like it.
Yep. uh. that'll do.
♪ He could picture the scene ♪
♪ Put his ear to the wall ♪
No.
♪ He heard one guitar... ♪
To the right... Ooh!
Goddamn.
Hold my blanket.
Hold your blanket. all right.
All right. you want to
load on the back leg...
Uh-huh.
-And then...
-Yeah.
Okay. I'll... I'll handle it.
Thank you. I appreciate it.
-I don't know what happened.
-Just do your thing.
Go!
You got to be quicker.
What are you doing. Dad? Hey.
Sobriety is a journey.
not a destination.
I believe in you. Happy!
♪ Someday he's going
to make it To the top ♪
♪ And be a juke box hero ♪
♪ Got stars in his eyes ♪
♪ He's a juke box hero... ♪
"What my teacher didn't understand.
what she couldn't understand.
"is that I only
cheated on the test
because my mother had yelled at me
about the oatmeal cookies. Yet again..."
Oh. there he goes.
Nice even strokes.
Thank you. Charlotte.
Good. Finish the louvers.
then do the borders.
Yes. sir.
Ladies and gentlemen. please
welcome Vienna Gilmore.
Everyone else sucks and
you know it! Let's go. V!
♪ Like a trip through the
past To that day in the rain ♪
Come on. Happy!
♪ And that one guitar Made
his whole life change ♪
♪ Now he needs to
keep on rocking ♪
♪ He just can't stop ♪
Happy! Happy!
♪ That boy has got
to stay on top ♪
Happy! Happy! Happy!
♪ He's got stars in his eyes ♪
-♪ Juke box hero ♪
-♪ Got stars in his eyes ♪
Boot!
Come on. baby! You're
back! Let's go.
Do you mind?
I'm sorry.
What the hell are you doing?
I'll take off. Have a good day.
Go back to your mobile home.
Got you a little something. Pop.
What? What is it?
"Thirty days sober!
Congrats. Daddy!"
You paint my house. brother.
Get him on the ground!
We'll put a little
extra into this one.
Happy! Happy! Happy!
I am so sorry. I did
not mean to do that.
♪ Juke box hero ♪
Damn you. Happy Gilmore!
I put a thermos of coffee in your
passenger seat. Dad. and a protein bar.
I love that. Thank you. Vivi.
You gonna bring back
another gold jacket?
Don't be disappointed
if that doesn't happen.
Just looking to
get in the top 30.
But that gets you enough money
to send Vienna to dance school.
You gotta do it. One of us kids
has to amount to something.
What are you talking about?
You're all something.
Something to me. Get
in here. Love you guys.
This is the first time you're gonna
be far away from us since Mom left.
We can FaceTime Dad
every day. It'll be okay.
-Yeah. day or night. You hear me?
-Yeah.
And I'll be back Sunday to
see you goons. I promise you.
Hopefully with one
of them big checks.
Hell yeah. Dad. Let's go.
Make sure John Daly
doesn't sleep in my bed.
If he does. no M&M's. Okay?
-Got it.
Arnold.
Jack-o.
Tiger.
SpongeBob?
What is that?
What's with the beaver teeth?
The truth can hurt sometimes.
-Oh. my goodness. Dougie boy!
-Happy!
I missed you. bro. How's
everything been going?
Oh. it gets harder
every year. Happy.
How's it getting
harder? I'm not around.
Yeah. honestly. the
Maxi Golf League.
The Maxi... I saw a commercial
for that. It looked stupid.
-Well. supposedly. it is faster-paced...
-Yeah. yeah.
...and our biggest sponsors are
suddenly slow to call me back.
I got a bad feeling about this.
We got the greatest golfers in the world.
That's what people want to see. the best.
Manatee says his
guys are better.
There's only one
way to find out.
Challenge him. People
would love to watch that.
Wow! Virginia really
rubbed off on you.
We had five kids together.
She rubbed off on
me all the time.
and I just laid there
like a sack of potatoes.
As charming as ever.
Hey. just get inside.
The guys are excited to see you.
Would you at least get Invisalign
for that thing? Thank you.
Hey. Happy. you gonna finish
off that blueberry jubilee?
Oh. God. Freddy's still snaking
everybody's dessert? Okay. you got it.
Thank you. Cheers.
I'm so happy to be with you. Look
forward to getting out there.
You gonna play tomorrow?
Why. you guys aren't playing?
Happy. these kids
are 20. 30 years old.
We're old and stiff.
We're old. but we're still cool.
You guys taking aspirin
before you get out there?
I'm popping them like Tic Tacs.
I grind them in my applesauce.
I used to be able to play 72
holes without breaking a sweat.
Now it takes me ten minutes
to get out of this chair.
Yes?
Do you mind grabbing me a half
iced tea and half lemonade?
Arnold Palmer.
No. Jack Nicklaus. but
I do get that a lot.
Fantastic. Be back in a jiff.
Happy. what gives with the comeback
attempt after all these years?
Well. I'm out of cash.
My daughter has an opportunity to go
to this ballet school in Paris. so...
Happy. I've known
you for 30 years.
You're like a son to
me. How much you need?
300 grand.
Good luck tomorrow.
Hit 'em straight.
-Excuse me. pal?
-Yes. sir?
I asked for a Tanqueray and tonic.
but they gave me Bombay instead.
I'm the busboy. sir. Sorry. I
will get you a server right now.
Uh. do you want some bread?
No. just the right
booze. thanks.
Okay.
I think I rattled him.
Hey. Happy. whatever happened to
that guy. uh. Shooter McGavin?
I believe he's still in
an institution. Jack.
Wasn't he friends with O.J.?
Well. they used to vacation together. I
don't know if they were friends. but...
This guy's losing it.
What are you doing
here? It's quiet time.
You suddenly got some very
powerful friends. McGavin.
This is a court order for
your immediate release.
Excuse me? Gentleman would
like new gin and tonic.
He said Bombay. no Tanqueray.
You told Spiethy
that was on me. man?
No. no.
You threw me under the bus.
So you could be the hero?
No. I... No.
You stabbed me in my back.
That's what time it is?
He just. he just said...
I can't work like this. man.
Watching my six all day. every day.
I just wanted to
help. I offered bread.
You mess around. you find out.
You're fired.
Fired?
Hey. pal. Yo. You think you
were a little harsh on the dude?
Sorry you had to hear
that. Mr. Gilmore.
You don't know the backstory.
Mr. Couples? More blueberry jubilee?
Nah. I'm okay. Maybe one more.
Yeah. Back in two.
Yackety-yack. don't come back.
Whoo!
Ah!
Shooter McGavin. I'm
such a massive fan.
Gentlemen. thank you for being
here at the Tour Champions Dinner.
That's what she said.
I'm not sure that made sense. X.
Every time our sport has overcome a
challenge. we have come out stronger.
Today's challenge is
the Maxi Golf League.
who allege that they are going
to make golf more watchable.
That's what she said.
-Great joke. Mr. Schauffele.
-Thanks. buddy.
I just got off the
phone with the president
of this new league.
Frank Manatee.
and I challenged him
to a competition.
Frank accepted that challenge
and then farted into the phone.
He did what?
What's the competition?
Our five best players
versus his five best.
Make it our five worst. It doesn't
matter. We're gonna smoke them anyway!
-Whoo!
-Yeah!
Now. I know that you all want
the honor of kicking their ass.
-Yeah!
-So how about this?
Top five finishers this weekend
represent us in the challenge.
All right. Let's go.
That's what she said.
Gentlemen. by showing
the world our dominance.
we will eliminate this league
before it even officially launches.
Let's go!
And now you've got something
else to play for. Happy.
Yeah! Yeah!
Gosh. I think there's
a fork in my ass.
Now that's what she said.
Yeah!
The sun is shining. The
greens are shimmering.
What a day to play some golf.
Welcome to the big one. the
U.S. Bank Tour Championship.
I'm Verne Lundquist. Here.
as always. with Jack Beard.
And the golfer everyone is
talking about. Happy Gilmore.
-Looks handsome.
-Yeah.
Gilmore returns after
a ten-year absence.
Some of the guys
set your locker up.
Bengay. Tums.
Preparation H. yeah.
MiraLAX. always good.
And. uh. diapers. Now
that's pushing it.
I know you never made
it to the Bruins. Happy.
but maybe you'll make this
five-man wrecking crew.
Oh. I doubt that. Tony. I'm actually
just worried about making the cut.
Mr. Gilmore. Sergio told me
you forgot to bring a caddie to
your first tournament. Is that true?
He said that? No.
Well. yeah. but still. I didn't
know the rules back then.
That's insane.
Yeah. that was silly. Can't
believe I would do that.
Hey. brother. Good to see you.
man. So here's what happened.
My regular caddie moved to
Switzerland for tax purposes.
so I'm kind of like.
I got nowhere to go.
What do you say. you and
me for old times' sake?
That's nice. Mr. Gilmore.
but I. unfortunately. I
can't caddie for you today.
You're not still mad about the
whole choking you thing. are you?
No. it's not that.
It's actually. I
don't caddie anymore.
I. uh... I play now. We're
actually playing together today.
I didn't know that. Blondie. All
right. well. I'll see you out there.
I'll see ya.
Blondie.
My name's Will. and I'm still mad at you
for choking me out. you son of a bitch.
We're minutes away
from the start.
and Happy Gilmore is apparently
breaking in yet another new caddie.
Uh. it's a club. Yeah.
Club. Oh. like
the club sandwich.
Not the club sandwich. Okay.
Let's check in with
our own Gary Potter.
who's with number one-ranked
Scottie Scheffler.
Thanks. Verne.
Scottie. you have
been on quite a tear.
My God. You're seeing
the ball and the hole.
and the position of the ball
and the hole... all good things.
Is there a question
in there. Gary?
Scottie. if you're the best. does
that make everyone else the worst?
I'm just gonna go warm up.
Always great catching up with
Scottie. Back to you. Verne.
Thanks. Gary.
The threesome of Justin
Thomas. Will Zalatoris.
and Happy Gilmore
is about to tee off.
Ooh.
Nice. Nice bang. JT.
Pressure's on with
Happy watching.
My family loves you.
I'm actually rooting
for you. I gotta stop.
No. Keep it coming. I need
all the love I can get.
Gotcha.
Now on the tee. Zalatoris. Will.
That's your name?
"That's your name?"
What an idiot.
I'm a little intimidated. All these
guys hit it big now. you know?
Do you need a water
refill? Any bread sticks?
No. Maybe I'll go
to my happy place.
Okay. I will be here.
It's not working. I
don't drink beer anymore.
Good.
Now on the tee. Gilmore. Happy.
Welcome back. Happy!
Golf fans around the world are
excited to see Happy Gilmore again.
but at 58 years old.
I'm not sure even Gilmore thinks
he can compete with today's best.
Hey. Happy!
I guess I need to
update my happy place
to something a little
more age appropriate.
Whoa!
You can do it!
Yeah.
Okay.
Thank you. Happy!
-Let's go!
Never did that before.
Thank you. man.
Okay. well. let's get... All
right. we're going to go.
-But you bring those. Those always come.
-Oh.
All right? That's it. that's it.
I'm sorry.
No. no. They got a strap if
you want to use the strap.
A snake! Get it off
me. god damn it!
Get the snake!
Come on. Come on. Come on.
Goal! Yeah. baby!
Come on. Happy!
Man. I don't drink.
How about some coffee?
That I can do! Let's
go. Let's go. Let's go.
Chug. chug. chug!
Yeah!
Yeah! Let's go! Yeah!
Holy shit!
Still the man. Happy!
It's my kids. Sorry. everyone.
-Good to see you. boy!
-There they are.
Daddy's on the tee... Wanna
see Daddy drive the ball?
Please. dear. Thank you. All
right. boys. This is for you.
Whoa!
Oh! Daddy got a
hold of that one.
What are you doing?
Gordy! You got to see
a doctor about that!
Happy! Happy! Happy!
Entering day two and feeding
off the fans' support.
Happy Gilmore has
jumped into the top ten.
Oscar. Where were
you? Who's this?
Oh. he's Esteban. my caddie.
-Okay.
-Steven.
Steven. nice to meet...
No. You don't get a caddie. Caddies
don't get caddies. I'm sorry.
No? Can he play?
What do you mean... He's not...
This is the pro tournament.
I'm sorry. He's gotta go.
Happy Gilmore!
Okay. got it. Okay.
All right. Ciao. Adiós.
He took his hat.
All right. go!
Okay. we got to play. man.
Let me have the driver.
Oh. damn it.
Wait! Please!
Now he gets it.
-Happy! Happy!
-That was the shot.
Daddy! Daddy! Daddy!
And heading into
Saturday. two shots back.
The comeback kid. Happy Gilmore.
Good shot. Happy!
Happy! Rules!
Happy! Happy!
Guys. what are you doing? I'm
trying to watch your dad play golf!
-Guys. we can't hear!
-Come on. guys.
No one could have
expected this.
Happy Gilmore.
From off the couch to the
top of the leader board.
And what was supposed to
be a nostalgic footnote
has turned into one of the best
three rounds anyone has ever seen.
The thing is. if I go for
this and miss the cup.
it's going to roll right
off the green. so... yeah.
-Okay. I see.
-Yeah.
What's a green?
Green? Know what? Don't
worry about that right now.
What I'm looking for is some
positive energy. you know?
Can I help?
Actually. you can. Remember
the happy place I went to?
-Yes.
-You go to yours.
Okay. I'll try.
What's up. man?
What do you got there? Honey?
What is this? What is this?
Is this about the
job? Come on...
Let's... That's...
Come on. man.
Oh. no. Not a bear. Not a bear.
Goddamn you. busboy!
-I'm happy now. Hit the ball.
-Yeah.
Yes.
You were thinking about a bear
eating that waiter. weren't you?
Yes.
-I thought so. Was there honey involved?
-Un poquito.
I love it.
Come on. Happy.
Oh. no. I don't see
that one stopping.
Wait a minute.
Zalatoris' ball
marker to the rescue!
Yeah. Blondie!
And the fairy tale continues.
Happy Gilmore has somehow
turned back the hands of time.
-No. Not again.
-Come here. Come on!
We gotta do it!
Oh!
I love it! Yeah. Oscar! Whoo!
Less than two months
after hitting rock bottom
in a drunken golf cart crash.
Happy Gilmore is 18 holes away
from a seventh gold jacket.
The only possible
conclusion is that
Happy Gilmore has reached
an agreement of some kind
with Satan. a.k.a. the Devil!
All right. Let's go! Happy!
-Good job. Mr. Gilmore.
-What's up?
In the zone today. Man.
We were putting. We were doing
okay. A little luck involved.
Hey. Mr. Gilmore. Billy Jenkins.
-Hey. nice to meet you. Bobby.
-Billy.
Billy was on fire today. I was
like. where did that come from?
Had the best round of my
life. I'm in second place.
You and me play tomorrow.
You're kidding. Look
forward to that.
I've never been in the hunt.
It's a dream come true.
You're going to love it.
You get in the top five.
you get to play against those
buffoons from the new league.
What's up with that tool
starting that league?
The guy came to see
me to talk about it.
He had the worst breath I've
ever smelled in my life.
Like somebody died in his mouth
or a donkey took a shit
there or something...
It was not good. Anyways.
I got to get to a meeting.
Love you. Bubba.
David. good to see you.
It's Billy.
So. in summary. I am no longer
allowed to purchase magic markers
in the state of Connecticut.
I am Nate. and I
am one day sober.
Nate. you're an
example to us all.
What?
Before we finish. I'd
like to say a few words
about the remarkable achievement
of our brother. Happy.
We've been watching you play.
Mr. Gilmore. So inspiring.
Yeah! Happy Gilmore. making
Black people like golf again.
That's right. Bessie.
I just hope Happy's able to
continue to play as well tomorrow.
Tomorrow being of
course... Oh...
Mother's Day.
Welcome to the final round
of the Tour Championship.
Here come your current leaders.
Journeyman Billy Jenkins.
getting his first taste of success
after an undistinguished career.
The only man in his way.
a golf magician named
Happy Octavius Gilmore.
Octavius is his middle name?
Nah. but it sounds
cool. doesn't it?
Wait a minute.
Can't wear shorts. Mr. Jenkins.
It's a two-stroke penalty.
That's okay.
I don't want to be hot
today. Makes my balls itchy.
Was that confidence or
just pure stupidity?
Now on the tee.
Gilmore. Happy.
Nice shot. young man.
Happy Gilmore will try to
defend his eight-shot lead
on this glorious Mother's Day.
Gilmore was aiming right for some
reason. and that's where it went.
A lot of holes left to play.
Yeah.
It's okay.
Mr. McGavin.
How'd you sleep?
This place... is amazing.
The pillows. the steam shower.
the free porn.
and these fluffy
pancakes. Oh. my God.
What do you say you
and I go on a tour
-and I show you what we're all about?
-Mmm...
I'll make sure there's a fresh stack
waiting for you when we get back.
All right.
Slippers on?
And why don't you throw
on some underpants. too?
It's all right. Happy.
Hey. Happy. Remember me?
My dad used to be your boss
when you worked in construction.
I'm truly proud of you.
Hey. thanks a lot. Mr. Larson.
Drago Larson.
Little Drago Larson?
Hell yeah! My God!
I always felt bad about what I did
to Daddy and the whole nail thing.
Actually. after
he got it removed.
he kind of missed it.
so he had it put back.
Oh. okay.
He passed away a few years ago.
I'm so sorry. What happened?
He rolled over in his sleep.
Oh. yeah.
At least I still have Mom.
Every boy needs his mom.
-Yeah.
-Happy have five kids. Mom.
Oh. tell your wife
Happy Mother's Day.
His wife passed away.
Oh. I'm so sorry. sweetheart.
Why didn't you tell me. Jerko?
Mommy. don't hit me.
Which club do you prefer. sir?
Let's go. Gilmore!
Give me... Let me have a wedge.
Let's go. Happy.
-Every boy needs a mom.
-But we don't have one.
You got it. Happy.
-You can make it.
-You got this.
Do it. Come on.
Oh!
I gotta go to the bathroom.
You came at a very
special moment.
Change is in the air.
What change is that?
Golf. New and improved.
Gilmore must love all this.
I wouldn't know. Happy
Gilmore's a broken man.
A broken man?
Yeah. ever since the
loss of his wife.
Wait. Virginia Venit?
Is that what her name was?
Oh. man.
Fart recognized.
All right. come on in.
Our current leader.
Happy Gilmore.
has been in the restroom
for an unusually long time.
Let's play some golf.
Billy Jenkins is playing
an inspired round.
Meanwhile. Happy Gilmore is
struggling to keep it in the fairway.
Cart path.
Wanna sip of my 3-wood?
-No. gracias.
-Okay.
You scratch it. I hurt you.
Thank you. Jesus!
Plenty golf to be played.
Happy. what does
Mother's Day mean to you?
Can you suck my white ass. Gary?
Just suck the entire thing?
Psycho.
Oh.
And it has all fallen
apart for Happy Gilmore...
Happy's... wasted!
...who is staggering.
literally. to the finish.
What I'm about to show you is
the foundation of Maxi Golf.
An X-ray from 1957.
Who's Ben Daggett?
He's the only guy who could hit it
farther than Happy Octavius Gilmore.
How come I never heard of him?
Well. he was a degenerate.
Couldn't putt for shit.
Just drove around the
country in the 1950s.
dominating long drive contests.
They say he could carry
the ball 500 yards.
One day. one of the mobsters
who he owed some money to
took a golf shoe and shoved
it right up Ben's ass.
And that's where
this X-ray was taken.
Do you see anything
unusual here?
Well. there appears to be a
shoe up his rectal region.
That's true. But see that?
That's the iliolumbar ligament.
Why is it in two pieces?
Let me guess. Shoe up the ass?
-No.
-No?
This happened much
earlier in his life.
Turns out Daggett severed it in
a childhood go-kart accident.
The separation of the ligament
from when he was a kid
increased Daggett's range
of motion in his hips.
dramatically improving
the amount of torque
and club speed that
he could generate.
That's why he could hit it
so far. Because of the shoe.
Will you stop with the shoe?
We're done with the shoe.
It was a go-kart accident
that severed the ligament
and turned him into a
long-ball-hitting freak.
And all those golfers outside?
We snipped their
iliolumbar ligaments. too.
That's cheating. Who would
agree to a surgery like that?
Journeymen... who were
good enough for the pros
but could never figure out
how to beat the legends.
It's all in the hips.
Grandpa. It's all in the hips.
Shooter. I want you to be
the captain of the Maxi team.
Hmm.
-Thank you so much.
-Absolutely. Mr. Manatee.
Pancakes next time.
And I haven't even showed
you the best part yet.
18 holes? Boring.
We do seven holes.
Slow play? We got shot clocks.
My God. this is obscene.
It's a lot to take in. I get it.
I will never have anything
to do with this...
This abomination.
You know. Shooter. it wasn't
very easy to get you released.
But it'd be pretty damn
easy to get you recommitted.
Yeah?
Damn. that's hot.
-I was told you liked it hot.
-Do you?
My eye!
Yesterday. Happy Gilmore had the
entire sports world rooting for him.
and then he took all that good
will and basically set it on fire.
-Go to your happy place!
-No!
He also lost out on playing
against the Maxi League
as he finds himself with
a sixth-place finish.
And so it is Jenkins who
will lead the five-man team
against the upstart Maxi
League. or... so we thought.
Sorry to pee in your
punch bowl. folks.
but I am actually a proud
member of the Maxi Golf League.
Bye-bye. regular golf. Bye-bye.
That's right. Billy's
part of a new league
where we hit longer. look
cooler. and party harder.
And the best part is.
our guys are "Maxi Good."
Give me the jacket.
My sources in the
DA's office say
Gilmore's actions
violated a plea agreement.
relating to his drunken golf
cart crash earlier this year.
and that he only avoided arrests due
to an ally causing a distraction.
Hey. Drago. you forgot
your underpants. Jerko!
Gilmore is now facing six
years in state prison.
but I hope the authorities will
deliver justice to golf fans
by sentencing him to the electric chair.
which at this point. he richly deserves.
Oh. Virginia. I'm sorry
you're no longer with us.
You were a woman working
in a man's league.
I bet that wasn't easy. Huh?
Yeah. I guess I should also apologize
for asking you to get me a Pepsi.
Diet.
Gilmore.
Shooter McGavin.
Last time I saw you. you were running
away in slow motion with my gold jacket.
That was my jacket!
Take it. I've got five others.
God! You would never have
won them if I wasn't...
What? In the loony bin?
You stole my life from me.
Now. why would I want to
steal the life of somebody
who eats pieces of shit...
-Oh. you...
-...for breakfast?
Game over. bitch.
-Come on.
-Okay.
-Let's go.
-We're gonna fist fight?
-Want this?
-Yeah.
You sure you want that? Come on.
Come here. now.
That was for you. Grandma.
I am so sorry I lost
the house again.
-Truly.
-Hi. Grandma.
Don't you ever
talk to my grandma!
Come on.
Jackass!
That was round one.
We are done. son. You can
tell everybody you won.
Should I put my hair
in a bun just for fun?
And play one-on-one
with Attila the Hun?
Oh. boy. That was
good. Round two.
Okay. We're even.
Come on. You love this.
-Get up. Absolutely.
-Thanks. man.
Okay. Hey. Are your hip
ligaments cut in half?
I don't think so.
Anyone ever stick
a shoe up your ass?
Not that I can recollect.
You realize these are
strange questions?
Apparently. if a certain hip
ligament is not attached.
you can hit the ball farther.
Oh. No. I always powered my drives
the old-fashioned way. With rage.
Yeah.
You want to get out of these
pajamas? I live around here.
Yeah. thanks.
Mister! Mister!
Get me outta here!
They issued a warrant
for your arrest. Dad.
Yeah. hide in the basement.
I should just turn myself
in. Get it over with.
-We'll ask the lawyer when he gets here.
-You hired a lawyer?
Okay. How do I look?
You look like my frickin' dad.
Yeah.
At least I'm not wearing that
ridiculous Bruins jersey.
Uh-oh.
Okay.
Okay. get the door.
Mr. Gilmore.
Mr. McGavin. John Daly.
Nice to see you again.
You're the lawyer? I thought
you were the IRS guy.
I was. but I got tired
of everybody hating me
and occasionally being
thrown through a glass door.
You hate me. don't you?
-Right.
-So. I went to law school.
You didn't want to be hated
anymore. so you became a lawyer?
-That's funny.
-Lawyers are snobs.
-Pieces of shit.
Let's sit. Lots to talk about.
Let me just have
a little shower...
This girl's got
some body on her.
Hey. we do not
objectify women anymore.
What?
Okay. great. Uh. looks like the DA
has withdrawn the arrest warrant.
What?
Even though you appeared
to some onlookers
to be inebriated
at the tournament.
you weren't administered
an alcohol test.
-And... I have better news.
-Yes?
You came in sixth
at that tournament.
That's right. I forgot about
that. How much did I win?
Uh. $496.000.
-Oh. my God!
-No way!
-No! What?
-Holy shit!
Baby! Yay!
Now you're really gonna hate me.
The tour is fining you
$500.000 for bad behavior.
So he lost $37.000?
No. It's $33.000. Dad.
It's $4.000. you buffoons.
How is that good news?
Well. you came in sixth. but
the winner. Billy Jenkins.
opted out of the tour team because
he's playing for the bad guys.
So you made the team.
-Dad. that's great!
-Whoa! Okay. Pop.
They don't want
me. I'm a disgrace.
A freaking embarrassment.
Let's go outside.
Dad. for a second.
Next.
Well. Shooter. due to
Mr. Manatee's sworn statement.
you are now technically an
escapee from a mental institution.
Welcome to the club.
Dad. it doesn't matter if you
play for that team or not.
You have to stop drinking.
I did. It's just...
Just nothing. You gotta
find peace somehow.
There's no peace. I...
The reason I joined
that tour again
was to get you the future you
deserve. and I lost $4.000.
You think if you made that money
I could leave you like this?
It's not your job to take
care of me. I told you.
-Of course it is. We're family.
-You're stuck with us.
Yeah. come on. Dad.
I don't want you to
be stuck with me.
You didn't do nothing
wrong. It's me.
I think this person could help.
Hey. you gotta put a
little mustard on that ball
so it doesn't get stuck where
the pirate hide his. uh. uh...
booty and shit.
The hold?
Yeah. the hold.
Get at it. kiddies.
-Thank you!
-Are you Slim Peterson?
That's what they call me.
Your dad Chubbs was my teacher.
My name's Happy Gilmore...
I know who you are.
Hey. you gotta hit it under the octopus
and bank it off one of his leg things.
The tentacles?
Yeah. testicles. Now.
what was you saying?
I need to talk to you
for a few minutes.
Damn. mosquitoes.
They everywhere.
-What...
-Look at them.
Alligator?
No. vending machine. I
didn't have enough change.
Had to reach up there to get my
Famous Amos chocolate chip cookies.
Man. looking at you just
reminded me of what I did to you.
What'd you do to me?
What I did to my own
kids. Stole a parent.
Man. you gotta forgive
yourself for that.
Don't want to.
I didn't want to
forgive you either.
because it was
easier to hate you
than to deal with the fact that
my daddy wasn't coming back.
It's kind of like I was
using hate to keep him alive.
But once I forgave you.
I became myself again.
And that's who I knew my
daddy wanted me to be.
You loved your wife.
You loved my dad.
And they loved you. period.
You know what else
they loved? Golf.
Oh. my God. yeah.
I talked to your little girl.
and she said you got a chance
to save the whole sport
by playing against
some clown league?
Yeah. well. why don't you
go kick some bozo ass then?
Let's do it for them.
I am so sorry.
Boy. why you had to
squeeze it like that?
I will throw these out. I can...
Give them here. I got
some Gorilla Glue.
Yeah. love you. buddy.
Yeah. man. thank
you for stopping by.
You know. we could
use some help.
Oh. about time somebody
recognized my genius. Say less.
Okay. okay.
Where do you think
you're going. Slim?
I'm going to help
save golf. Charley.
If you leave now. you ain't ever
coming back. you big pork chop.
Damn straight I ain't never coming
back. you fine-ass English hillbilly.
Welcome. gentlemen.
You are the five golfers
who will represent our tour
in the grudge match
against the Maxi League.
I don't have to tell you how
important it is that we beat them.
And here to talk about how we're going
to accomplish that is Shooter McGavin.
Thank you. Doug. I'll
take it from here.
I want to talk to
you about pressure.
Now. as the most successful
golfer of the '90s.
I've faced my share. believe me.
but nothing like my
30 years in the can.
And if I let my guard down
there for a nanosecond...
Stab!
I got a shiv in my guts.
Anyway. I hear you guys all
have ice water in your veins.
Well. I reviewed the footage
and I ain't seeing it.
-Man. what's happening right now?
-Uh...
Bryson DeChambeau.
2022 Portland Open. Eighth hole.
You got a two-stroke lead.
You got an opportunity
to pull way ahead and...
-Aw!
-What?
Huh?
Oops.
Come on. We all miss a
putt every now and then.
Scottie Scheffler.
Oh. boy.
2019 Cadillac Invitational.
Third hole. You're tied.
Top of the leader board.
It's Sunday. Pressure's
on. And you...
Hmm. Into the woods.
The woods. Scottie?
Are you afraid to win?
-What about you?
-What?
Yeah. 1996 Tour
Championship. Final round.
Don't do it. boys.
No. This isn't relevant.
Four-stroke lead
on the back nine?
The guy who beat you
got hit by a Volkswagen.
-Jackass!
All right! Maybe I haven't handled
the pressure perfectly myself.
but I have seen the surgically
modified freaks that you're playing.
I have seen the monstrosity
they're making you play on.
And if you can't take the heat.
golf. as we know it. it's finished!
So let's do this!
Come on. Let's put them in.
All right. On three.
-One. two. three... Shooter!
-Golf!
Time to prepare for
a moving target.
The cups are gonna be moving?
Damn it. Rory. Nothing's
off-limits for these commies.
-Now. Oscar's cousin...
-Esteban.
Esteban is fast. And
elusive. I'm told.
He's gonna start
at the red flag.
If he makes it to the blue
flag. we haven't done our jobs.
He's cool with us hitting him?
Yeah. He's been paid.
What did he say?
You're never gonna hit him.
Oh. yeah? How come?
I'm shifty!
Okay. he's shifty.
He is. I've seen it.
♪ Get your biscuits
in the kitchen ♪
♪ I'm a sous chef on a mission ♪
♪ Baby. wiggle
it. it's vicious ♪
♪ We about to break the dishes ♪
♪ Got the pepper
with the sodium ♪
♪ We cookin' with petroleum
Come step up to the podium ♪
It's too easy!
♪ And cut up this linoleum ♪
Yeah!
You got me!
Come on. cousin.
You're almost there.
Okay. stop! We got
him. We got him.
I said stop! Who did that?
Oscar. You sicko.
-So I got a hockey question for you.
-Uh-huh.
I notice when the players fight.
one of the guys is always pulling the
jersey over the head of the other guy
-before he starts pounding on him.
-Right.
-Yeah.
-Is that hard?
-No. it's easy. You want me to show you?
-Yes. please.
Brother. Can I borrow
you for a second?
Basically all you do
is pull the shirt over.
This traps the arms. You know?
-Yeah.
-Knockout. Money.
-You sure?
-Yeah.
Okay. How much?
Fifty.
Uh. I'll give you a hundred.
Here we go. You know what I mean?
Yeah. That was nice.
-Okay. Money.
-Okay. You got it. Scottie. I'm broke.
-Thank you.
-There you go. Okay.
Great job. today. by the way.
-Excellent. Yeah. it's fun.
-Yeah. That was easy.
I love my job.
Mini-golf-style putting is about
two things. angles and obstacles.
If you can read the angles.
you can avoid the obstacles.
Let's putt so we can
figure those angles out.
Yes! Scheffler!
Yeah. you're right.
One more day before we face these
chumps. This is how I used to toughen up.
Oh. my God. Rory!
Okay. Oscar. let's
see your stuff.
♪ Sittin' down is stupid
Now let me see you move it ♪
Oh! Do you want bread sticks?
A batting cage to toughen up?
I love how much
we're in your head.
Oh. I think we're in
your head. Brendan.
Otherwise. you wouldn't be
snooping around and following us.
My name is Billy.
Hey. settle down. Barry.
and get off the electric
Royce. No leaning.
Look. Happy. I don't want to
have to humiliate you tomorrow.
You're in the DNA of my league.
The way you rebelled
against the traditions
and fussiness of golf.
it was beautiful.
So I'm gonna offer you one last
chance to be a part of it. okay?
Hell no.
And you look like Freddy Krueger
worked at Starbucks. Change it.
I'll give you 10%
of the company.
I can't believe I'm the one
sticking up for tradition. but...
My wife liked the way
golf was played. as is.
And she was pretty much
right about everything.
So sorry. boys. but tomorrow.
your dumb league is done.
No. tomorrow. I'm gonna finish
the revolution you started.
I heard what you said about
my breath to Bubba Watson.
I have gingivitis.
It's hereditary. okay?
And I got it from my
great-grandfather. So I'm so sorry.
I'm literally
smelling it from here.
And the wind is
blowing that way.
Something has to change in
your life. I'm telling you.
Okay.
Come here. Bring it in.
I just wanted to say thank you guys
for always getting me back on track.
-I love you.
-Love you.
This ain't about Vivi going to dance
school. It's about saving golf?
Maybe we can do both.
but we will figure
that out. I promise.
Because we're Gilmores. and
we don't know how to stop.
Hell yeah. Pop. let's go!
And don't forget to feed
John Daly three times a day.
-Okay.
-Got it.
-Love you guys.
-You heard him.
Let's do this for Mom.
-For Mom!
-For Mommy.
-You got this.
-That's right.
That's right. She deserves it.
Go get 'em. Dad.
Pop...
-All right.
-Yeah!
-What's going on?
-Let's go.
-Go Dad. you got this.
-Go Daddy!
-What's going on?
-Stupid.
-Damn it.
-Are you kidding me?
What are you doing?
What's with this guy?
What you doing
hitting my dad's car?
This is a family affair. bro!
Take him down. boys! Let's go!
-Whoa. whoa. whoa!
-What's he doing?
Get him!
Chase him! That's right!
-Where you going?
-Get him!
What the hell is happening?
Welcome to an event unique
in the annals of sport.
A one-time showdown between
golf's greatest players
and the wild upstarts who
seek to supplant them.
Let's get it on.
Welcome to the Maxi
Tour Challenge.
I'm Verne Lundquist. along
with my partner. Jack Beard.
and my new partner.
DJ Omar Gosh.
Truly bitching to
be here. Verne.
Ladies and gentlemen
of planet Earth!
Are you prepared to
have your minds blown?
I'm tippy-toeing. I said
I'm tip... Thank you.
I said are you guys ready to see some
golf so exciting your heads will explode?
Whoo!
Here are the Maxi Golfers!
Go Harley!
We've got Harley...
Flex!
Screech!
8 Ball!
And Tour Champion Billy Jenkins!
And now let's welcome
their opponents.
the Basic Vanilla
Regular Golfers.
Boo!
♪ Goodbye to you ♪
Holy shit! Is that
Shooter McGavin?
Look who decided to show.
You never finished your
pancakes. by the way.
You want coffee
in your other eye?
Ha! Get a furlough from
the Funny Farm. Shitter?
-Laugh it up Blue Balls.
-It's 8 Ball!
Your name's Davis Miller. You're
my brother's college roommate.
It's 8 Ball now! Tell
him I said what's up.
You guys get these clothes from
the Lost and Found at Comic-Con?
Did you get these melons
from your mommy? Yeah?
Don't twist my boy's
titties! Those are mine!
Hey. I'll twist your
head off. slap-nuts!
Break it up! All
right. knock it off!
Golfers. we have a
seven-hole course.
First up. Mr. Scheffler
going up against Mr. Harley.
Ladies and gentlemen.
let's play some Maxi Golf!
-Let's drink up! Come on. let's go!
-Yeah! All right! Whoo!
-Here.
-No. I'm good.
-You got your own.
-Mmm.
-I want to try that.
-Mmm-mmm.
And so it begins.
hole number one.
Best of five matches. so we only
gotta win three of them today.
I say we sweep
these goofy bitches.
-That's a good idea.
-Yeah.
The fairway's a forest? I don't
even know where to lay up.
Or you don't lay-up.
and you crush the ball
500 yards over the trees.
Whoa.
And Harley clears
the entire forest.
You ain't number one
on this tour. chump.
You smell like my stepfather.
Let's go. Scottie. Come on.
now. Let's shake that off.
You the man. Scottie!
Miss it! Miss it!
Quite An impressive
right cross.
but Scottie Scheffler is
going to be disqualified
before ever swinging a club.
Whoo! That was
some gangster shit.
Gangster shit indeed.
There goes the sweep.
Yeah.
Oh. no. not again.
-Come on.
-I know the drill.
-Bye-bye!
-Sorry. boys.
We'll take care of
business. all right?
Next on the tee. Rory
McIlroy and Screech.
Screech?
They call me Screech
'cause that's the sound my chainsaw
makes every time I tear up a golf course.
Isn't Screech a character
in Saved by the Bell?
I'm not familiar
with that program.
He was like the comic
relief on the show.
Yeah. like the white Urkel.
Nobody cares about
that '90s shit!
Those guys do.
I love you. Screech!
Let's just play Maxi
Golf. all right?
The rest of the Maxi team has
no problem clearing the trees.
The regular golfers.
not so much.
Go. go!
Hold on! I'm speeding!
-There it is! Right there!
-Yeah. okay.
Oh. my God. There goes the 8.
Shut up!
Here we go! To the right! Whoo!
Yeah!
Looking a little
tired. Bry-Bry.
You're looking like you
wanna go for a swim. Davis.
This is the new golf.
Bryson. and it's 8 Ball!
Where's my ball?
Bad shot. Happy.
This'll make you feel better.
How about you take just a sip?
Wow.
We're doing a breath contest?
Yeah. I'd walk away too. pal.
McIlroy's tee shot landed
in the right bunker.
which. like much of this
hole. appears to be on fire.
Screech!
Yeah!
Viva regular golf!
Hey. man. I'm gonna
change the channel.
Frankie. sit your ass
down. We're watching golf.
All right. I'm sorry.
Get in the hole.
Oh! Wow!
That's what I'm
talking about. baby.
God damn it. I just washed that.
It seems like nothing is
gonna slow Gilmore down.
All right. See you try
and beat this one. Happy.
Let's go. Gilmore!
-You jackass.
-What the...
Oh!
Are you kidding me right now?
You just cost me the hole. dude!
Happy Gilmore.
Man. I wish my father
was here to see this.
Ya jackass.
Jackass.
-Jackass!
-There he is.
Unfortunately... ...he's in
the great Sizzler in the sky.
Know what? I don't
miss that dude at all.
What are you gonna
do. Happy boy?
Unless you wanna go to jail.
you can't hit me. Jackass.
Oh. my goodness!
Yeah... but we can.
You guys came?
This your posse?
-This is what I do.
-Okay. let's see.
There's only four of you?
Better go get some help!
Okay. Okay.
-Come on! Get him up. boys!
-I know a lot about fighting.
I'll bite your leg off.
You want some smoke?
This ain't nothing. Now
you got me really pissed.
Oh. what is this? You
want some of this?
Look at the gators!
You brought the whole family.
Oh. my dick!
Oh! Whoa! Detroit!
I just don't give a...
Put some respect
on my name. bitch.
-What is he doing to those gators?
-Jackass!
Well. it looks like we
have our first fatality.
Whoo!
If you can believe it.
the Maxi Golfers are
up two matches to one.
which means Koepka and Gilmore
are going to have to win out in
order to defeat the Maxi team.
All right there.
Flex! Come on. Flex!
Boom!
-Nice shot. hottie!
-Ooh!
No pressure. Boobs Getchya.
Next on the tee.
Brooks Koepka.
To me. the smartest play is to
come up short of the icy green
and give yourself a
chance to chip it in.
Yes! Oh. God!
Sorry. guys. I knew I
shouldn't have fist-pumped.
Sucks for you guys.
Another disqualification.
Game over.
No. wait. In the event of an injury.
we have the right to substitute.
All right. fine. Fine.
Who you guys got?
The one and only.
What's that now?
And a wild day just
got a bit wilder.
Shooter McGavin will take
over for Brooks Koepka
here on the sixth hole
and the putt from Flex.
Oh. it's off course.
I think I see an opening.
Let's go. Scooter!
Clock's a-tickin'!
This is a joke. I'm not a
competitive golfer anymore.
What are you talking about? You
still got the shooter in you.
That guy's long gone. Gilmore.
No. He's sleeping. It's
time to wake him up.
Look at these
punks. The B-lists.
-Never won shit on the real tour.
-Yeah.
And now they're laughing
at Shooter McGavin.
the greatest golfer of the
'90s. except for me and Tiger?
How dare they? How dare
they disrespect you?
Where should they go?
-Back.
-Back where?
-Back to...
-To their what?
-To their shanties.
-Aha!
Because this is whose tour?
It's Shooter's. Shooter's tour.
-Whose tour?
-It's Shooter's tour!
-It's Shooter's tour. baby!
Yeah!
He's got the old
pistols back again.
-Give the man his lob wedge.
-Oh. I'm feeling it now.
No pressure. No pressure.
You're not gonna make
it. Shooter. Tick tock.
-Five. four...
-No!
...three. two. one!
You've got to be kidding me!
Oh. my God!
Well. how do you do?
Shooter McGavin jars the cup.
wins the hole and his match.
Shooter! Shooter!
Come on now! Choke on that!
That leaves us tied
with only Billy Jenkins
and Happy Gilmore
left to be decided.
And it's come down to
this. The final hole.
Winner take all. The
shot clocks are off.
The pressure is on.
The future of regular
golf hangs in the balance.
Thousand-yard par four.
That's a little long.
Not for me. big man.
Yeah. Check this out.
Hello?
Woo-woo!
Whoa!
That is the longest
drive I have ever seen.
Hey. you remember
my name now? Bitch.
I'd like to forget ever
seeing that hip thing.
That was disgusting.
Jenkins can be on
the green in two.
while Gilmore has no hope of getting
on in less than three strokes.
Verne. that sucks.
Okay to use that hate
one last time. Slim?
Yeah. let it all out.
Ain't no surgery for that.
Come on. Happy. let's go.
You never made the Bruins
because you suck at skating.
You shut your stupid face.
Who's he talking to?
Oh! And your daughter's
never going to ballet school
because her dad's
a washed up drunk.
I'm gonna kill you!
Uh-oh.
Somebody went further.
Yeah...
Bitch!
Jenkins is first to hit.
Yes!
Oh. and by the way. all
four of your boys are dumb!
What did you say?
-Ow! Ooh!
-Aw.
Yeah!
I can't believe there's
taxis without drivers.
AI girlfriends. and now. quite
possibly. the end of traditional golf.
I'll go first.
Give you a chance to think about
how you're going to play that.
-Whoa!
Billy Jenkins. you stepped
on it and stepped in it.
Shut up. Edward Woodenhand.
Screw you. Cabbage Patch Kid.
Take your time.
Go get my lob wedge. Wait.
Go stand right there.
Okay.
Right in the back of the cup.
-No. don't get off! God!
-Oh!
-Vecsey!
-What?
God damn it.
Excuse me. Know
what? You're fired.
Makes sense.
Will you quit messing this
up and make this? Come on.
I'm trying. sir.
Just get it on the right line.
Coming right up. sir.
And Billy Jenkins
is in for four.
-Yeah!
-Choke on that one. Happy!
Gilmore has only two shots
left to even tie this thing.
I'm not even playing and my palms
are sweaty. Mom's spaghetti.
I can't get a damn
swing off here.
You got any ideas?
We're in trouble. dude.
Hmm. I say ricochet that shit.
Yeah. that's a good idea.
Amazing!
Did it go in?
Not that amazing.
You nervous?
No. just... Can I
use your mailbox?
The question now is.
how do you hit on a
green you can't stand on?
What do I do?
Here we go. Dad!
-Dad. let's go!
-Let's go! All you!
-Right now!
-All right.
What's the plan?
How about this?
Go to the other side
directly across from me.
-Yes. sir.
-Okay.
-Oscar. Hey.
-Yeah. go!
Oh. God. I can't bear to watch.
Oscar. how much do you weigh?
170.
Pick up the bag. please.
Actually. take two clubs out.
Two clubs. Two. Two clubs.
Okay. Pick the bag up again.
And on the count of three.
we're stepping on the green.
-Okay.
-Are you ready?
And one. two... three!
Whoa. oh... Hey...
That's it. That's it. Okay.
we're gonna hop forward.
One. Two. Three.
Ooh.
Okay.
Now to the left.
One. two. three.
That's it.
Now we're gonna go
sideways... Two. three.
Ooh. Oscar... Nice work.
Check this out.
Whoa!
-What's happening?
-What the...
Sorry. Happy. I had to. We
don't do tiebreakers at Maxi.
How about we raise the stakes?
I end this whole project
if you sink this putt.
And if I miss?
It's simple. You
join Maxi League.
How about this?
You pay for my
daughter's dance school.
buy me my grandma's house back.
plus I get your Rolls-Royce.
plus you gotta buy Oscar
his own restaurant.
What kind of restaurant
are we talking here?
What kind of food. Oscar?
Sushi. No. no. no. Italian.
Fine. You're on.
You heard it. There'll
be no playoff today.
Oscar. I have bad news.
I'm holding a sand
wedge. I need a putter.
Just take it slowly
out of the bag.
That's it. That's it.
Take the sock off.
Okay. so we're gonna throw it to
each other on the count of three.
-Okay.
-We can do this.
One. two. three.
-Oh!
-Okay. I caught my own club.
Physics is a bitch. isn't it?
Here's what we're gonna do.
We're gonna throw it
straight up in the sky.
Let's do this.
Do not get sick. Oscar.
-Okay. One. two. three.
-One. two...
Yes!
Let's go! Let's go. Hap!
High five. High...
Hey. Gilmore can do this.
I've seen it. I lived it.
Wow. Cool. How bout we
take this to the Maxi?
He's gonna fly off.
-...spot. focus on the spot.
-You got it. Focus.
Oh. no.
Hang in there. Oscar. please.
Come on. Dad. You got it.
Dad!
Come on. Dad!
I love you so much!
Do it like my daddy taught
you. Tap it. Tap it in.
It's got a chance.
-Go.
Come on. Happy.
-Come on. come on...
-Come on. come on. come on...
-Get there!
-Oh!
Oh. no!
Yes! Welcome to
Maxi. Happy. Whoo!
Oh. my God! Happy
Gilmore has won!
And regular golf will live on.
-I'm 8 Ball! I'm 8 Ball!
-No! That doesn't happen!
You are a piece of
shit. you know that?
I did everything I could...
Oscar! We did it. Oscar!
Papi. papi. Wake up.
-Good job!
-Did we win?
-Yes!
-All right!
Happy. yes!
Yeah. yeah!
Stop.
Your training paid off. You did it.
I'm proud of you. I'm proud of you.
-Yes!
What a great win.
Let's go to Hooters.
-Happy Gilmore! Happy Gilmore!
I can't believe I'm saying
this. but you're all free to go.
Beautiful.
Unbelievable. Tremendous.
I understand you
have a restaurant.
We have the best Italian Dominican Puerto
Rican Cuban restaurant in the town.
I love my new job!
We did it. baby!
We did it for Mom!
Well. I've won a lot of trophies
and jackets over the years.
but out of all of them. I have to
say this is by far the most special.
And I want to thank all
my friends out there
who helped me achieve
this monumental moment.
Three months sober.
Yay! Way to go. Mr. Gilmore!
Splendid! Splendid. Mr. Gilmore.
But will you make it to a year?
-Magic 8-Ball says... unlikely.
-Uh-huh.
What are you talking about. Hal? Happy's
going to make it a full lifetime.
Know what else is
full. Charlotte?
My gutters. Full of dead
leaves and squirrel droppings.
But you'll be cleaning
them out this weekend.
I don't like the way
you talk to that kid.
It's fine. Mr. Gilmore.
No. it's not fine. That kid has
helped me more than you have. Hal.
Seriously. Mr. Gilmore.
I got this.
Guys. can we be done
here? We've got enough.
Why are you talking into
your collar? Are you high?
Are you high?
-Holy...
-Whoa!
Hallowicious Lieberman!
You're under arrest for
fraud and extortion.
We got enough footage of you
being a sick son of a bitch
to lock you away for a lifetime.
You narc'd on me?
Guess so.
Hey. man. I was just trying
to help these people.
Manual labor's
therapeutically beneficial.
-Hey. Happy.
-What?
-Catch.
-Oh!
-I believe that's Mr. Gilmore's!
-He got my coin!
I got the coin!
-Oh. shit! Stop!
-Stay still!
You're a very cool kid.
You're a very cool guy.
You remind me of my dad.
Yeah?
All right. just
have fun in Paris.
If you get homesick for America.
I can ship over some
Yodels or bottle rockets.
Whatever you guys want.
We'll be fine. Dad. And we'll
see you next month. right?
That's right.
I got the British Open. I'll show
up a week early. we'll hang out.
I want to see some fancy
French dancing from this kid.
Then you can come
check out our show.
What show?
We're gonna be singing mimes.
I thought mimes aren't
allowed to talk.
That's how we're gonna separate ourselves
from the other mimes. by singing.
Okay.
♪ We're trapped in a box! Now
we're tugging on a rope! ♪
♪ Even look at our sister... ♪
-And we'll kill you!
-And we'll crush you!
-I'll murder you!
-Don't you look at her!
-Smart. I love that!
-Nailed it. Really good.
Come here. Gonna miss you.
And if you're hungry on the flight.
enjoy the bread from Oscar's restaurant.
Go crush them over there
for Mom. Have a ball.
Love you. Dad.
-Hey. here you go.
-You're the best. guys.
-Sir. right there.
-There you go. buddy.
Yeah. get him!
I'm so sorry. sweetheart.
Come on. Vienna.
Love you. I'll miss you.
♪ Tuesday's gone with the wind ♪
Hey. Happy.
Oh. You're okay.
♪ My baby's gone with the wind ♪
♪ Train roll on ♪
♪ Tuesday's gone ♪
Battery. zero percent.
I didn't charge it! Damn it!
♪ Oh. baby Don't it feel
like heaven right now? ♪
♪ Don't it feel like
something From a dream? ♪
♪ Yeah. I've never known
Nothing quite like this ♪
♪ Don't it feel like tonight
Might never be again? ♪
♪ Baby. we know better
Than to try and pretend ♪
♪ Honey no one Coulda
ever told me 'bout this ♪
-♪ I said yeah. yeah ♪
-♪ Yeah. yeah ♪
♪ Yeah. yeah. yeah. yeah ♪
♪ The waiting is
the hardest part ♪
♪ Every day you
see one more card ♪
♪ You take it on faith
You take it to the heart ♪
♪ The waiting is
the hardest part ♪
♪ Well. yeah. I might have
chased A couple women around ♪
♪ All it ever got me was down ♪
♪ Then there were those
That made me feel good ♪
♪ But never as good
as I feel right now ♪
♪ Baby. you're the only
one That's ever known how ♪
♪ To make me wanna live... ♪
Well. the bad news just
keeps coming for Maxi
and its controversial
founder. Francis Manatee.
Since the spectacular failure
of the Maxi Golf League.
the popular Maxi Sports Drink has
been recalled after complaints
it caused irreversible
halitosis. gingivitis.
and a new condition
they're calling tongue rot.
We at the Sports Hole tried
to reach Manatee for comment.
but his current whereabouts
are apparently unknown.
Yeah. I would run too if I gave half
the world midnight booty breath.
Hey. Scheffler. it's been three days.
You sure you don't wanna make that call?
It depends. What's for dinner?
Chicken fingers.
I'll stick around another night.
Okay.
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Get your biscuits in the kitchen
I'm a sous chef on a mission ♪
♪ Baby. wiggle it. it's vicious
We about to break the dishes ♪
♪ Got the pepper with the sodium
We cookin' with petroleum ♪
♪ Come step up to the podium
And cut up this linoleum ♪
♪ Just move it ♪
♪ Move it ♪
♪ Sittin' down is stupid
Now let me see you move it ♪
♪ Get your peaches off that
stoop Baby. work that hula hoop ♪
♪ Throw it back and watch 'em
shoop Scottie Pippen. alley oop ♪
♪ Mix it up like orange drink
Shake your buffalo chicken wing ♪
♪ Get your galoshes. make it rain
Now-now let me hear you sing. uh ♪
♪ Just move it ♪
♪ Move it ♪
♪ Sittin' down is stupid
Now let me see you move it ♪
♪ Just move it ♪
♪ Move it ♪
♪ Sittin' down is stupid
Now let me see you move it ♪
♪ Sitting is dumb ♪
♪ Dancing is more fun ♪
♪ Sitting is dumb But
dancing is more fun ♪
♪ Dancing is more fun
Dancing is more fun ♪
♪ Just move it ♪
♪ Move it ♪
♪ Sittin' down is stupid
Now let me see you move it ♪
♪ Just move it ♪
♪ Move it ♪
♪ Sittin' down is stupid
Now let me see you move it ♪
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-